It's time for another Marie Mour video because I got some new outfits, harnesses, also in patent leather this time and in red and a bodysuit and a catsuit that is really just fashionette.
So I think this is going to be a really cool video, awesome looks and I don't know, let's just start.
I think I'm going to start with this one because I love the patent leather look. It's shiny. Let's go.
I changed into it. It took me a while. The mesh catsuit or the fishnet catsuit isn't the easiest one to get in. And then there are so many buckles you have to close and adjust because it's completely size adjustable.
I wear the size small but it's so variable still and I just love it. It's a classic Marie Mou outfit like strappy harness, a bra piece this time and a leg garter and yeah I put a fishnet underneath.
But you can also check out my other Marie Mou videos. They also have mesh bodysuits and different styles. So this is the first look for today.
and I think it is really nice it looks so high quality I mean it is high quality it's patent
leather it's really nice and shiny we have Marimur embossed in the leather they have their own
metal hardware the rings have Marimur embossed it is such like a nice outfit and if you put it on
you feel like this is like something extravagant. I think it's also a cool look with my new wall here
and it looks so great. It makes such a great figure. I do not feel restricted at all but if I
would want to feel restricted I mean there are handcuffs missing. These are part of the outfit
so let me check if I can put them on by myself.
Now you could of course just link them together, so it would be like this, but the clue here
is that you have a linking piece on every side and you can for example attach it here
on each side. And now then this would be the look. Or you can attach it to the leg harness
or something on your neck or even something on your feet. Or maybe not you but someone
Anyway, let me just unclick these, because I feel like there's something missing here
on the neck, so I want to try something and pair my Swedish collar with it for a complete
look.
Here we go, let me check.
Yeah, I think it fits.
I think I'm just making so much noise with these things and now with this collar.
But you wouldn't wear it on the streets anyway.
I love this outfit.
I think it's really cute.
I also kind of love that the bodysuit slides over the shoulders.
I don't know why, it's just...
I prefer it that way.
Yeah, I put it on a few times by now, the bodysuit, and it's still in one piece.
I did not destroy it yet.
It's a good quality fishnet bodysuit.
And I think I will change into the next outfit now and I'll go with the bodysuit here.
And then the red as the last one.
A bodysuit without harness set this time.
and I think it's one of my favorite bodysuits ever because I love the cut. I think it's really
nice and unique way to spice up a normal bodysuit with the cut out here and also the arms which are
attached like a shrug but yeah not a separate piece. Also from the back it looks nice
and it's just really comfy. I feel good in it. And that is what this kind of fashion should be about.
Be yourself, feel good in it, feel empowered and wear what you want to wear. The material is really
stretchy and also super comfy it's kind of a spandex lycra mix and it's a bit shiny
so I like it I also like the finger how do you call it finger loops the
fishnet catsuit had that as well and here we have it again I think it's a nice
way to ensure that the arms are not riding up here and out too short which I
like. So I was thinking if you do not want to wear this just as lingerie what
else can you do with it? And I put a skirt on top of it. That way you can
basically wear it as a top and I think it's a cool look. I think that's
definitely something I will wear in summer when it's a bit warmer outside.
It's cold at the moment, it's still so cold I want to go back to summer time and warm weather.
Anyway, how do you like the look with this skirt? I think it's quite cute.
Checking the mirror. Yeah. Also, I can do it a bit more like this and show that there is something going on here.
Or just like this. Anyway, both work. I quite like it. And I do have one outfit left.
It's the red bodysuit with a red bra harness leather part and I'm going to change now.
And the last combination in red and since it's super see-through I am wearing undies because
this is YouTube and I don't want to get banned or deleted or whatever and yeah
this is the outfit. I love that it is a bodysuit which is bust free but then
there is this leather bra I put on top of it which makes a nice look with the
delicate mesh here and the leather with the metal hardware and the top part. I
think it's a nice combination. And I paired it with some red over-knee boots
because why not? All red. I love to pair bodysuits with over-knees so I don't
feel too naked. And I think it's a nice combination. I do have a discount code
for my new so check out the text under the video and also click on the link
there to their shop. They have loads of cool stuff. These leather stuff, the body suits
and so much more to discover. So have a look at their shop and use my code if
you buy something for yourself, for your partner, as a gift for someone else or to
yourself. Everything is possible and I hope you enjoyed this video. Tell me in
the comments which one was your favorite outfit. I think for me it was the first
combination with the bodysuit, the fishnet. Why do I keep forgetting the word fishnet today?
I don't know. The fishnet catsuit and the patent leather harness combination,
followed by the bodysuit from Second Alfred and then this one. But I also love this. It's also
cool because I have so many Marie Moire outfits by now and I've worn them to parties so they're
not just laying around I've worn at least three different outfits to different fetish parties
that's how I like to go there and that's what I like to wear there so if you need inspiration
check out my channels or the Marie Moire shop Marie Moire I don't know anyway I hope you enjoyed
this video. Have a nice day, see you in the next one. Bye!